Nice answer.
Well, you guys, the last night was kind of a disaster.
I was on for a bunch of hours and then the last minute, you know,
I got overwhelmed.
Someone said they were caged, but it was always already chaotic.
Yeah, you know
A little bit of drama but guys I have funny stuff to show you today
I've been like playing with this
Music generator more right hey ball way, you're in love with still
At this website
Freakin so I'm really most thinking about subscribing to this website
Because it's really really good, I just
Was expensive I ordered a bunch of stuff today. Hi, you know, uh, hey
then
Hold on. I forgot. I'm going completely blind now. I need glasses now. I can
Hold on. I cannot see
Okay
Yeah, yeah today I have just woken up and I had a half a donut
Had a look at doneness
Yeah, you don't love this song I have oh my glasses though. Oh, yeah. Oh my gosh the lens is falling out
Here
Guys want to hear your glasses on yes
Okay, you guys want to hear the song though. I want to get 20 people in the room. I'll play the a I'll play the song, okay?
See I just want to make sure I
Yeah, my songs
Okay
When you hear the songs, let's play the song
I wish I would show you and like uh
More you love music. Okay. Well, I don't know if you heard the first song we made but here's the next uh
Next song is there one ready? I'll wait till 20 people get in here. You can listen to this hear the song
I'm gonna probably play this a few times not not in a row, but
Come on guys. It's the one just left the room. Come on. We're running to
Here's this okay. You're gonna love this. You're gonna love it
Yeah, okay, so it's almost
It's really cool is that you can
Basically, it is like so it sounds really good. You love it. You love it. I promise it's so good. It's funny
I just put some input like what the song should be about like little things and then it's like it puts them in the song
Do I know who just yeah is
Hmm. No, I don't I'm maybe a her for I'm not sure
Yeah, do you guys hear me? I'm sorry. I'm fine
Better I don't know if you can hear better. Okay. I don't know if my microphone is on but I'm sorry
Okay, guys, I have the debut of this song. So so as soon as 20 people come in here, I'll play it
Background
Ready okay here, I will play you guys here, okay
Hold on. Hold on. That's as loud as it goes.
Okay, ready?
9 p.m lights up nice hot chaos in the stream beat it calling in slurring words starting up the scene talking all that trash
Then she flips race queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Scythe puts it laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurred flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chat's on fire can't tame the flame this ain't your mama's podcast. It's a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up Scythe
Michael getting dawned, Alex taking flight.
It's wild, it's wrong and we do it every night, yeah.
He's got him simping, heart's in the chat
but she ain't got time for a dude like that.
Trying to put in hard, let the girls react.
It's a free show party, no filter, all fax.
Yo, all fax.
Yo, yo, Michael drops a line, gong, not tonight.
Alex tried to choke, boom, sent into the night.
Panel looking sideways, someone's got a fight.
Producers on mute, praying this don't spike.
Diamonds feeling the fight, these shirts slipping down low.
Oops, she says, win or wake, and that's the whole show.
Sight happens to leave us still cracking jokes.
Slurred out wisdom with a bourbon soap glow.
No rules just rolled, we pretend to play.
One hand on the mute, other letting it spray.
It's a circus, a riot, a beautiful mess.
Welcome to the madness, buckle up Scythe, boots matching on camshafts losing their minds, Michael didn't gong, the Alice taking flight, it's wild, it's wrong, and we do it every night.
Hey, I'm sniffing hearts in the shaft, but she ain't got time for a dude like that, diamond flirting hard, let the girls react.
It's a pre-show party, no filter, all facts, yeah, all facts, lights out one more round.
Feet is on the line, yelling at it goes from a bottle to wine
We laugh, we cry, we crash, rewind, same time next week
You know the vibe
Welcome to madness, enjoy the ride
Welcome to the madness, enjoy the ride Welcome to the madness, enjoy the ride
Oh
Whoa, oh my god, I think it went excellent a little bit overboard with that one. I mean wow
Wow guys
You believe that isn't that good
So I think maybe we can actually maybe make a CD for I don't know if I can buy the rights
I'll see maybe I'll get a license for this ship
How was it you like it
Hey babes, I
Made it I made it I made it. I mean I wrote it with that. I wrote it. I put in the some input I
Who the heck wrote it I wrote well AI wrote it
But I put in the input like I put in like the suggestions for what it to be about
You know and then it like writes the song
CHTPT wrote the song and then I put I put it through an AI music generator
That's not me it's not me seeing it's a it's all AI it's all AI it's
Guys I hired a professional band I it cost that cost $20,000 to make
I mean it's pretty pretty cool what they can do nowadays, huh? That was like a whole
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's it's a it's a joke it's a joke because it's so it is like good like but it's like it's like so like
So good. It's like crazy. It's like wow. It's like unbelievable. How good how good they are. Where do the captain contents music?
I think so
It's called AI music gen dot AI I think
Yeah
And yeah
You're cool, huh? Captain content. Yeah
I'm the captain now, but I think I'm gonna, you know, all right
I'll be able to write people music now all right about you know, at least uh, you know
I'll send Lisa's long school because she began to become a big Spanish musician
Captain content what hair products do I use? I look like I use very many hair products. It looks like I use
You know oil
My hand my hand is my best the best products
But pair process I use okay
First thing I try is the
Captain content at least I mean at least it's a pretty good music. She's a better musician than captain constant
I think you hated that the arc the captain content arc
Okay, I can't wait to somebody that's in a song shows up on the piano. That'd be so funny
All right, I'll read more songs with other people's names in them. I'm sorry and it's like and then it was like I was trying
It's like I was saying it's a big
Like thing doesn't I can fix it and stuff
But it's actually stick it kept saying sag and it sounds like spike and so there's big lines in the song about
big but it's but it kind of works because
But me it's called jizz. What?
Yeah, yeah
I'm waiting for, like, Bita or something.
So I can play the song.
Well, Bita or Paige or, who else?
Yeah, pretty much there are the stars of that song,
I would say.
That song, oh, and through Surya Diamond, of course, too.
If either of those people come,
I will play the song again.
So I don't want you guys to figure this out, but it's my second song, you know, the second song, the other song is like
Kind of like a rocker. It's like, you know, the more I've read you, I'll probably think oh the old ones suck
And I'll think the new ones are good, so I'll probably get better
It's called jizz instead of jazz you're saying Nick
I don't know my um kind of should be a good day because I got my order a bunch of stuff
That will help me like see my house and stuff like that like, you know
Yeah, we were like, um, you know
It's her Jen. I got new uh, yeah a bunch of stuff
A lot I got
Um, look, I don't like that is where are these people?
Yeah, but I went to my I went to the hidden people today. I didn't find anybody really hidden and so you're good
You know, I know you had some issues this morning
We also had some issues with like, you know people being really rude on form bombing and you know
I mean, it's just whenever people do that, it's just like a portion of the system doesn't really do anything to me
I mean, it's like you got your new tarot. Oh good. Congratulations. Yeah, you can start just pulling a card a day
Congratulations. I hope you enjoy
The other thing so let me see that yeah cars. I hope you enjoy so let me see I can draw to draw people
Let me see I can draw people in the chat so I can draw. I'm gonna try to draw
Okay, I'm going to try to draw a size picture. Okay, I'll draw a picture of you shy. Okay. Okay, there we go
Okay
We're doing a, I mean, I get,
I'm gonna draw a picture of you, okay?
Hey Baldwin, thank you for becoming a member.
Thank you.
Take a picture of Baldwin, I'll do it.
So, are you ready?
Do you wanna see it?
S-H-Y, hold on.
Shy.
Shy, are you ready?
Are you ready, thanks?
Okay, I'm just shy.
Add your names in your hair somewhere,
S-H-Y, it's a jaw in your hair.
Like that you look like oh, I drew you're here too long. Hold on
You're too long
No, this is just I am the town flash is known as the flasher. Oh good
That's Tom flash is known as a flasher who's Tom flash on point that looks like you're okay
Thank you. You like that? Oh, okay. Hold on. You like that?
That is Cheyenne. I can do anybody else. I mean, I say, I say, do I think?
You like that one? Okay. I'll save.
Cool. Okay. That's cool. Okay. Good. And I'll do Baldwin's and she, if you remember. Okay. So Baldwin.
Hold on, I need to darken that.
Hmm, okay. Yeah, so woman. Okay, I
Don't know if this will work. Okay
It's a mask, but I don't know if you can tell it's your mask. There you go
I'll go this is a
Be Baldwin be be be
I tried to make it a mask like, you know.
I don't know if I did it myself.
He thought I was being a reading and not drawing.
It's for shy, not shy in.
Oh, I don't know your name.
Oh, I'm sorry, did I say shy in?
Okay, you guys, she's shy, she's a little bit shy.
Okay, it was accurate.
I just kind of picked, I hope it kind of captures
The feeling of it a little bit. I don't know if it's accurate
It's okay, okay good. Okay. Thank you. Thank you so much. I'm sorry you forgive me
call Alex video
You like the Alex video call Alex video it was beautiful
Okay, no person can I draw a person? Let me see. I need to draw a person now
Okay, I got that
Okay
Yeah, I got I got this
Is that clear?
Hey, bro, did it do your hair? Hold on.
There, I gave you some nicer hair.
Where's your heat off?
like that. Hey, how you doing here? This is not a beard, it's a key job.
That's perfect, okay.
I bet I give you a heart shoe.
Amazing.
Isn't my talent amazing as it's basically you know, I think I get I do get an essence
But that's like I don't like I don't know if I have the accuracy down
But it isn't in my mind. It does look in it. It's how you look before your morning shave. Hold on. Yeah
Look at KV dying to be included. Oh
Yeah
Black Archie you're gonna hear this you'd hear the new song you're gonna wish you know, I put you in the song
I'm gonna put you in the next song. Okay guys get to make a request. Maybe you know
Maybe I'll create the next song. You know, if you really want to be in it for sure
Like I really let me know but yeah, I can add people if I want to
You draw you in love shoes with blue eyes or light hair. Well, but your name is blue eyes and light hair
The love she was I like I mean that's how you describe like Mike
Oh shit, okay. I don't know if I hope I see poppy there. Nameless. I don't know do eyes and light hair
Oh, I don't have to color here. I'm gonna color the color
Select template. Oh, I saved I got it back on save it
Okay, oh
This is just like a little this is called Zen. It's like a little
Our program you can you can just like you see this like
Okay, love she was with blue eyes. Okay, let me put darker. Okay, there we go
Love she was so that means like love she was kind of a bruise safety the McQueen. I mean, I'll play the McQueen be a bit
I'll play I'll play a little later
Oh, okay. Well
Love she was home
Oh my gosh
Sorry. Hold on.
Okay, there we go.
Left sheath, no eyebrows. Oh, okay.
I don't, I mean, I've tried my best. I'm low sheath.
There's this is like, okay, there's the arms. There's Checa
Magic trying to do like a
Imagin this is a dress and they can wave away the way you're waving
Nameless name is nameless
How's that? Press your hair so you're going to tend your eyebrows.
Here your eyebrows, there you go. Is that better? Perfect, okay, get it. I'll save that one.
Okay.
It was pretty good, okay. So who has someone said,
Okay, that's really you that you or who is that?
Yeah, I drew big big no, we say big they say yeah, I drew a great one. You see I'll draw a jug
It's just a
He looks a little bit happy, okay
Here's how I imagine okay
That's Doug. It's a bit easy. Easy. You have to hear the new song. It's so funny. Nice teeth.
Yeah, that's Doug. That's Doug.
Even darker hair. Okay. Hello, hello, hello. You'll love the new song. We need a beta and page
Oh, you're welcome that you look like you you see it's a very it's not mine. I'll build upper lip. There you go
They look weird. Oh, well, they say I'm now looks like a mustache your mustache like that
Yeah, you do have a mustache, okay, I'll fix it
I can't fix it oh shit
Okay, well, that's fine. It's fine. It's time to be connected. We got your big Polish nose. I'm sorry
Okay, your big Polish nose, okay, let me see. Let me see if I can see that you see
This is one offensive home.
OK.
Hold on.
See.
Jen, hold on.
I'm sorry my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my my
You do the reading you got a lot of cards that love you've been working yourself a lot awesome. That's awesome. That's what it's about, you know
It's okay, we all we all type of this once in a while
Nameless get you into that net to dreads. Yeah
That's my eyes on these other drugs imagine that's just content. Okay
Guys if you have a request, you know
I will I draw anything you'd like to.
What kind of braids?
Well, I don't know.
Let's see.
Does that look like her?
Is that good?
The form rolls?
Ah, that's kind of hard to do, but I'll try.
French braid?
Okay.
Okay, save.
Not a very good, you look, I didn't do a very good job.
Sorry.
I don't know, cornrows, yeah.
I guess I can, I don't know if I can do them very well.
Try this.
Today I'm worse than worse. I know I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
Rogues tanny think you may start yourself. Yeah, you guys are amazing. How is that kind of art? It's kind of lost
I called a lot of friends here. It's a good one. Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I
Had made it too thick. I
Made your day. Well, how much this is for you guys
Who was that that was just that someone said someone said that was like yeah, that was like dreads. Oh, yeah
I'm trying to like think I must be like it's like
Well, I bet it's coming out like dark
Like this, you know
Then you can go
Maybe like an Amish, Amish kind of thing.
Oh, thank you. Triline's going straight back. Yeah, I, I, I'm sorry guys.
Aw, he's dropping with dreads. Spiritual, you're not racist. I can't, well...
I don't know. I'm not good at, I just, guys, it's hard to draw, I'm not like that detail where I can draw these, like, detailed, like beautiful dreads, I was like, I can just, like, just draw, like, you know, doesn't look very, I'm better at, like, drawing, like, giving, like, the feeling of, like, the, um, look, looky, I want to do lookies, but let me do yours, okay.
Um, I'm, yeah, okay, so let me, I'll do your, I'll do your looky, okay.
Okay, so this is good because she's already kind of like a drawing a little bit. You see so you just have to
So I'm gonna have this like
Hmm
Let's put a G on your forehead for the low key. Okay
Like this, huh?
I like that
That's fabulous. I know it.
Old movies are the best. Oh, you're welcome. You're welcome. Hope you enjoy.
Do you remember that?
Sorry, not perfect.
Matt! Oh, shit! Fuck! I was hoping I at least get a laugh. I got a laugh, so okay.
Okay, everyone know you didn't laugh, you didn't laugh. Okay, shit.
It was Matt. Oh, I didn't do a nose, hon.
Okay, I did your nose.
I'll give you a notice, okay?
You're welcome.
You started a race as a more by mentioning the word.
Well, why would you do that, Sean?
Why would you start a race as a more?
Well, just stop mentioning that word.
The nation passed away.
Oh my god. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to laugh. I didn't mean it's okay. It's okay
You know, you know at least big nice is not here to see the racism or she would have been so sad
She was such a such a heart for you know
RP Naisha you heard the she became that I know but then she didn't she like escape
She was it was broke your heart. I know all of us all of us
Okay, guys, you know, you're here for each other
You're trying to say you were the racist, the dreads or spirits.
I know, I know, I have, I think I have, I've verified, I think I've verified that Cheyenne
is, well, you are, I'm at least 18, hopefully, I think the Ignatius was stacked, yeah.
Yeah, she was 500 pounds and you know, she was she was rejected for my 600 pound life
She was not heavy enough, but she was almost there. She really wanted to be on that show meet doctor now. Okay
Hi, hi, Rana introduced me to
To shy and
Shy yeah shy you have to you know, I think guys work for
Yeah, I know it's like so if anybody like you know, if you know if you have any information that is otherwise
Yeah, no, yeah, exactly
By the American games
There's no information, you can't, yeah, okay, let's not fight guys. Guys, are we ready to hear
the song? Is a Vita page or 30 diamonds? You know, and the panel's 21 and over, I can't really
control who's in the chat, right? If you're a kid, if you're definitely a kid, you are not able to be
I can't control who's in the chat. It says like participating in the chat is for 18 and over, please and
That is it's playing for 21 over on the panel. We'd like to come up. Okay
Come on up
Piranha introduced me so I hope
Yeah, be it. Yeah, I
Is in safe dating flirty diamonds. Yes. No, no, it's a
Regine's even
What do you think guys? I mean it's like in the bush. I think
These things are reciprocating chat. I don't know but you know, I dealt with some
People of different personalities kind of
Seekers dating flurry diamonds. Oh my god
Hi, I think that is he's the key
Yeah, please I do not
It's a participate in chat 18 or over please if you're not over 18. Just like we're not participate in the chat
HK Memphis is mentally and hey, okay, okay
So they are dating okay, you got sigwas now is it um raging demon
Okay, here's Justin. Oh, I just make sure this is the real Justin
Oh
Hello
Justin
Justin I
Don't hear you. Oh, yeah, I hear you. Hi. How are you? Are you doing man?
Okay, yeah, it's a real
Yeah, fine, I got four on this morning. Yeah. Oh god by who
Um, the same guy, you know
His name is Tony or something like that
He always laughs. He always laughs, but it's okay
There's a lot of
I just think of that like the hundreds of hours of the show that I've done that are just like, you know
They're just gone in the ether. It's like kind of like I had to delete them just because you know someone
I didn't ruin my show and so I bet it's okay. That'd be a no harm no fell. I got no
No, no
Penalty or anything for the form wrong. So that's good
Yeah, how are you today? Okay? Yeah, I'm doing wonderful. It's like hey, I was I thinking you know
You know if you know I'm banning everything and he has you know a lot of subscribers
I bet you he has like a lot of tips, you know to grow your channel a lot, you know if you wanted to
Yeah, I mean, it's like yeah, I've talked to okay. I mean, I'm basically
Hey, you go viral. I mean, I need to go viral basically to like get a lot of feel like something
I would there'd be something along the way some get some video or something
some some my show go viral somehow and then
That would be a way to get a lot of subscribers
Otherwise, you know, I don't know. I
Think he just went viral. So here's LES. Oh, I remember this person. Okay
Hello, what up psyche? Hi. How are you? What's up? Yes? What up? Who's that?
This is Justin on the line
Who?
Justin just in Boil. Yeah. I'm a new here. I'll yes. This is this bunkies bunkies a boyfriend
Yeah
So if you've heard anybody very hit on spunky this guy wants to beat you up
Okay. Who want to be? Who want to be up?
Spunky. You know who Spunky is? No, I don't know who's funky, punky. What? I don't know who's that. Okay. Never mind.
Obviously, you haven't watched the show too often.
I don't know. I don't know who's
who's who's who's who's who's
Okay. Yeah, Miguel awesome. I like Miguel up Barry. They don't like I'm not okay. So yeah, so guys I
Have a new yeah, I saw I was waiting for one of the people in the song at least to like be in the chat
It's what it has to be beat a page. I you want to sing a song sing a birthday song
No, I'm not seeing a birthday song because it's not his birthday. Is it send me send me a birthday song today's my birthday
Okay
I
See it like Marilyn and Marilyn Monroe for you
You don't see the label it says what is it a book? What does it say picture look at the picture?
Hold on. I don't know if it was a decent to look at. Let me see. So look at it and we'll see. Oh, it's a demon
It's a happy birthday alias run in new york. Oh
So it says yeah
No, it's like it's like giving the finger and it says something else. It looks no have you zoomed
Uh-huh. Oops. Hold on. What did it say?
I'm sorry
Okay, well happy merry unbirthday. How about that very unbirthday?
So you have a lousy action in serious. Okay. Okay. Um, so yeah guys even even you song to play though
You love it. You'll love it or
Yeah, you do
Let's sir, let's sir, L-E-S-R, that's your name, let's sir.
You can't be, guys, when it gets here, I can play the song.
I'm fine with you, right?
I'm gonna talk this morning.
We're fine.
We're absolutely fine.
We're just gonna have that relationship where we're like...
What's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up
And guys I'll make I'll make some more songs. I'll do a whole album for my fucking show and they'll be a good song
They're good songs. I mean, they are like, you know
You know, they need to AI, but it's like the pre-sumford
Yo, why yo, yo, yo, I'm thank you. Why are you in your panel? Yes?
Because I got perform bombs, sir. No, I'm talking about last night
That was last night. Oh, you mean the night before last right in the panel. Well, you're talking about like eating like I
like
It's really disgusting things and then it was a little bit of seeing what happened was your boy with the penguin hat the one we got the penguin picture, right?
Uh huh.
Well with the cops use right and put it in my my my my booty and I'm like what the
And then he's hanging on block
Yeah, I know and then you started you started getting like really like, you know, I've seen it
It's like you kept going with it. Okay. We're going back and I was like, oh my gosh
It sounds like a see like difference or something. It sounds like, you know, it's too much thought of me for my show
Too much thought of me. It's okay. It's okay. Thank you. Just uh, you know, it's kind of like try to keep it later
If you was trying to get on some sleep, she is exhausted mostly message. She's been going through. I know. Yeah, okay
I keep punching out where this is the job.
Yeah, yeah.
If you hear me, the music now,
I have full songs written about this show now.
Ready to hear the song?
I should be able to sleep, I'll just play it.
Do you wanna hear it?
It's kind of a hip hop song.
Are you interested in hearing it?
Okay, I'll put it on.
Are you gonna hear it everybody?
Justin, are you there, LES?
Yeah, I'm still here.
Yeah.
Okay, here, here, I'll play this song.
I won't play the whole,
I'll just play the chorus of the song.
Hopefully you can hear okay, okay, there's the song.
Okay, never mind. I have to find it. Okay, I'll find I'll do it later. Let's continue talking. So I
Have written some music
So how is your day, it's okay. So how have you been since then like a since that show, you know everything was
But I hope you had a good night and day and you know yesterday. I got porn bombs
So there's no shows left over from yesterday. Unfortunately, you know people
Do that really our staffs? Okay?
For me it's like the lowest lowest form of life AI
Music, okay. Here's the music. Okay
Get ready guys, here we go.
All right.
It's 9pm, lights up, nice hot chaos in the stream.
We'd be calling in, slurring, we're starting up the scene, talking all that trash, then she blips, raise queen, mad at me.
Girl, please, the show runs on caffeine, psyched with it, laughing loud with it, in its veins, slurred by left and right, we got the beat, no shame, but the chat's on fire, can't tame this flame.
This ain't your mama's podcast, it's a runaway train. Welcome to the madness, buckle up, psyched, team session on camera, chat's losing their mind.
Okay, what's going on, okay, hold on.
Yeah, I
I'll try to I'll probably subscribe to this. Let me see me. I'll subscribe and I'll just like I can play it
I can finally work correctly
And either was you and others to make other song. I guess that's probably the best thing to do
I mean, it's just kind of
I have to do if you're seeing Sammy will talk people
Excuse me, Sammy Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-Wu-W
Wow, so let me see so this you've been okay, so I
I guess I need to
Yeah, I want to I love these AI songs, but it's like
Kind of like I'm trying to figure out how to like
Download it and it's expensive. It's like $13. Well, you know for a month
I guess that that's actually a good price if I could download the song, but it's like
If I keep commercial, let me see, let's see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let me see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let me see, let's see, let's see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me
Okay, I'm gonna subscribe then. Well, how much time is make sure I'm not from my account, but yeah
I'd be really excited to play these songs and make some more. Oh shit. Oh
I was in the stream. Is everybody there?
Do everything you're worried. Oh, yeah, I think she's all right. Yeah, okay, so let's do it
So I can do it
I have a couple songs already and then I come up CB
Yeah, come on up everybody like everybody's welcome to come up. Yeah, so I guess it's a good deal. Um, so I will
Get this membership so then I can share
music for you guys
I have a lot of questions for you psych about DMT, okay, ask me
How many times have you tried it or done several probably like probably over 10 over like 20 times probably
I've made it two times too. I can make it but now I have a friend with
They have a DMT pen like like the bait pen and it's like so strong and it's just so easy and stuff like that
You know, I really recommend
If people know how to make the vape pens look into making DMC vape pens
If you're making DMC or DMC, I'll be down live. Yeah, okay, so I'm gonna sign up for this
Thanks, $12.90 a month. Um, yeah, that's done. Okay, how many times did you break through on DMT?
like
They got like how like you're talking about going through like the astral project or like the body or like
Like how do you mean like like like like did you get to the point where you've seen the
machine elves and and that kind of stuff or no I've seen I've seen like things around
me change I've seen things in my mind as it's talking to entities and things like that just
I've seen things out of the corner of my eye.
I've had three counts on it.
I've, as for visual hallucinations,
I would say probably I need to do the stronger MAOI
inhibited dose of DMT, that's kind of an hour long trance
kind of thing where, I've had very strong doses,
but it's hard because it's like, you're like,
It's like such a new world that it's like you're not used to like navigating it. It takes a while to like be able to like navigate it
It's the night in here in the link. Okay. God pin the link. Yes. I will pin the link
Oh
Yes, like like what is your view like do you think that that's just the mind doing that or do you think that that's an actual place that you're going to
We're already there, it's like a perception, it's like we're there and we have one perception
of it and it's like what was really there is a lot more than just our perception and
our perception is kind of selective too, and what we like to block out a lot of stuff that
Maybe is there I mean it's like there's so there's a lot. It's just like it's just us ignoring stuff
That's or that's there because we would be too much to take in if we like consider all that's actually there, right?
What do we have here?
Or just talking about
drug experience
Do you think maybe like DMT very?
Do you think DMT like that?
Maybe kind of like like removes the filter that we have on our brain
Yeah, it was like it's in our brain naturally. Okay, it's a part of our and
And then it's also released in like a larger quantity, but we're about to die and so it's like
It has something to do with death. I guess I think also with the even Egypt like DMT
But this hasn't had them. There's I don't know. I just think of I think of snakes
I keep thinking of like the DMT serpents
I there's like and like the whole like everything is a serpent like the air turns into a serpent kind of kind of like
First the Milky Way is like a canal like a serpent teeth canal. You have lollipops the birth and death. Yeah
Birth and death. Yeah, they're in your birth and death. You probably we see the I know but people we usually start hallucinating
you know kinds of crazy shit right before they pass away because
It's like it eases the transition. I think I think that it's kind of more of the truth
But you see in psycho circuits on salvia. What's what's it? Yeah, you know, it's like fuck it
Watch some brush the right music videos. They get the right stuff to watch
I will ask you to remove their rights. Okay. I will I will since I see there, you know, yeah, I mean, I just don't have my
India, I'm sorry
I'll take off right now after you did DMT like like did it change your view at all about about if there's like life after death or
or not at all I
Um, I know I believe in you know in eternal life. I know you don't you always are commenting. Oh, yeah
There's no life after death. So is that something that you picked up from GMC or do you like why do you why are you so sure?
There's no life after death because you always are like
Saying oh, there's you know after life is that's it, you know, right? But is there more what do you think?
Yeah, I just I don't know you know I've seen
Decent amount of dead bodies in my life and you know like looking at the dead body
It's just like I just feel that there's that there's nothing there
And I kind of feel that at like a death that it just lights out and we basically go back to like before
We were born which is like pure pure nothingness and then like that's just it for eternity. We're just gone
I don't know. It's just my view
Yeah, you know, it's like
It's kind of like a, well, if you have that kind of view, I would find, you know, and I was very into like Satanism, which is like, you know, Lebeson Satanism is basically like, you know, hardcore atheism, you know, with like a God complex, sort of.
But yeah, like, so, you know, I've seen like the negative kind of like, you know.
like, world view, like, you know, like, not denialism, which is like, you know, life is meaningless.
You know, it's just like humans are animals. It's a very kind of like...
Well, what's the point then it's like it's like then you can just basically do whatever you want do it that will you know
She's like, you know, okay, but it is supposed to like do it that will you know in accordance with your higher self
Not like it's whatever you want, right? So they has good and bad. Yeah
I mean it was interesting, but it's like it was just like atheism is kind of like just empty words like okay
So it's nothing means anything so why it's what's the point of anything like just this like, you know, just do it
animal if you want
But otherwise, you can try to go for the higher stuff.
You have lollipops in your fridge.
Yeah, OK, so I'm going to get this on a grid.
Yeah, that that's actually my view psych is that I kind of you know everybody looks for meaning
But you know I'm kind of the point where I don't think there's any meaning at all
So I don't know but that's that's actually an all plate
Okay place to be at but then like part of me thinks
But but then to like psych like part of me thinks you know like everybody thinks that that there's a beginning and an end to everything
But like what like maybe maybe there isn't maybe all this is always been here
Right. I mean, yeah, maybe it's like, you know, people think it's like, you know, like a like a line where it's like
There's a beginning in the end. That's the line, right?
I mean, it's like a circle where it's like a continuous cycle or maybe it's like a spiral where it's like, you know
It's spiraling out like more and more J. Shut your dumb ass up
Well, who's who who?
Jay
Okay, Jay. Oh, yeah, Jay's it's talking in the chat. What are you saying, Jay?
No, the one on panel the profile picture says Jay. That's just him
That's bucky's boyfriend. You can read just your bifocals motherfucker
You cock sucker you you old bitch
Your wife don't think that oh
Your mama don't think that about me. I go deep in those balls deep in that fucking pussy every night boy
You go balls deep in fucking sights asshole balls deep
You heard tell them tell them
Don't be fucking saying you heard that's my shit. No, that's mine. That's my boy
What are you now? Now you calling me boy on are you racist? Huh? What you part of the Ku Klux Klan motherfucker?
I'm a Brooklyn motherfucker. Why don't you come up here talking all that?
I'll be up there. My name my name fucking saying man. My brother named Julio motherfucker come find me
That's my real name
Where you at? Which borough you at?
But why would I tell you that shit nigga meet me at the fucking live bird
Meet me at the fucking park
Motherfucker, I live right by the live bird. Meet me at the basketball park or school your ass
And then I'll kick your ass right afterwards motherfucker
Duncan you make you lay in the fucking ground like a bitch that you are
Motherfucker you ain't from fucking New York. You don't even sound like you from fucking Brooklyn. Okay, you sound what you just moved there
Yeah, I did
Me from fucking Brooklyn
I'm from Chicago motherfucker bitch asshole
It's like where you find this motherfucker
Um
On your mama's bedroom boy
What's up, what you say though man, I ain't mean to stir shit up man, you know
Thank you, sir. I'm fine. I've just been
Doing it is just rain been crazy the fucking New Jersey right now is fucking flooded. I got my peoples up there and they got
Crazy
Yeah, I guess he
Maybe but he wasn't bringing on to the table anywhere in p3. Okay. Good. Okay. Good. I have
I cannot download this music
Awesome
Wow guys, so I mean I'm about to like fucking be able to the place of music
Or yeah, these songs I now have the rights to these songs. Okay, so
What up with the chat, what up north cow, what up Vicky John D. Gabb was good
Nameless New York native
What up with y'all man, look why the fuck you crossing the lawn you fucking dumb bitch get the fuck out the way
Damn
Did you hear I'm hearing
Betas
Yeah, yeah, I mean I was on her a panel earlier and then she was on KK's for a little bit
by the fact she was on there until KK got off so but uh
Okay
Being in a lot of like pizzas and
Dead rats. She got a dead rat yesterday. I did rat was it a rat or the snake or was it both?
No, no, so the packaging has a snake on it, but it's it's a snake food. So they just have the snake
But it was a fro it said it KK looked it up and it's a frozen rat
So I was dead, but I thought I really did
I thought that's that snakes eat live rodents like a lot live rats. So
Is the fucking audio fucking up is it me?
I'm trying to add some stuff to the studio right now. Yo, so there's so a new thing with stream yard
If you click on the chat like if you if you want somebody stream yard like I'm on yours
It will tell you like how many people are backstage it won't tell you who but it'll tell you that there's that there's a
People backstage. Yeah
Said that they said oh, there's people waiting backstage
Hold on hold on well, I might be wrong because right now saying there's three people so do you have somebody backstage right now?
No, it's just me. It's me on my
Tablet I'm trying to add some things by tomorrow. Okay. That's what it is
And so if you have a another screen backstage, then it's a it shows up as another person
Okay. Yeah, I'm missing the backstage adding something to the to my to my media
Okay, so here I'm back. Yeah, cuz I see you had you had subscribed now on the corner. How the hell you do that?
That is if you
They have these live if you go into if you're on stream our premium you just click on add more like add more media to your media
Sections and it will have already stuff there like you can just add for free and then I think that's one of them like they have
some stickers and stuff they say like you know if you could be like that you can add this one it says like you know
Like share subscribe right there. You can say like welcome right here
you can say
Q&A you can also download packs and just add them to your stream already. I guess again, but
breaking news and be right back
Holy shit, so stream yard. That's why they raise the price then yo tell me why I'm still paying
I got a fucking
notification that they took 49 whatever it is 49 90
49 99 for my account. I'm like, I don't even go live man. Yeah
Yeah, we'll cancel it the time to cancel it and then we'll offer you like 40% offer the next six months
And you don't have to pay it all at once you pay it like just a month at a time
It'll just take down the price like 20 bucks a month for every month you like to renew, you know
Yeah
Because I'm not even using that shit the last time I went live was on a holiday. What holiday was it?
I did an eight hour live and um that was the last live I did
I think you can like um you might be able to also um you can um get that back
but you didn't go live last month or something
you didn't go live
Then you should be able to just say just either just be with the credit card company already wore with them
And they'll just agree to fund you for the month. He did use that. Yeah, cuz it is like kind of very expensive
Wow, yeah, I'm an OG. I was on this motherfucker when that shit was cheap as hell
Like and then they went up, you know, I mean they are adding like the chat
But the thing is I got a feeling that they're gonna make the chat where you can like
Make it bigger or they just gonna make it bigger themselves. You know what I mean, but
Yeah
Because you can't really see the chat like it's pointless to have it on the screen if you can't really fucking see this shit
Unless you got the if people watching, you know, you on a TV, you know on a 50 inch
But you can't really see it
Okay, so I can add some music, I think, let me see.
But why are you doing that?
But fucking, Bita have been going ham on Kate, and then Kate announced that she was taking a little break.
I heard she was in your chat, though, earlier.
Somebody sent me a screenshot where, I guess, Bita was going back and forth with Kate or whatever,
and she tried to join your panel, but she didn't let her.
Or whatever she says backstage, which that's the case and that's what's up, you know fucking
Hey, who is back to be their case? No case says she was back stage. Oh, yeah
I know but then yeah, that was a form bomb
I mean I literally she was on the show one time and then she would came on and then I then
Then the fake came on and she formed on me. Yeah, oh
Be careful
Okay, so I have
Add this music
I think if Kate taking a break then that's gonna kill fucking the content for
We're a little bit the only thing I can see coming something coming through is fucking crystal Marie and beta
But that's the Marie don't want to fucking join be the fucking panel
And be the guy something going on with crystal Marie
So that that's only gonna happen probably on same man shit cuz crystal be over there and then be the good pop up
Shit, I'm sorry. Hold on. I'm gonna say I'll fix this.
Uh...
Uh-oh. How do you fix that?
Oh, shit, shit. How do you... How do I fix this?
I deleted the fucking... that clip.
Shit, I deleted the fucking...
That, and so now it won't come off. Shit.
In the trees, on the side of that highway.
I'm gonna fucking...
Alex.
What are you gonna do to me if I...
Ah!
Um, fuck, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I
Okay, yeah, check it out. I'd like you
Yes, I'm already ahead because I got OBS
That's how I'm able to like play videos while I'm on your panel when I'm home or whatever because I'm using OBS
but uh, I'm sure it ain't gonna be nothing more, you know, I mean, it's probably gonna be the same shit that OBS provides
And OBS is free so
But if you're doing everything off your like tablet, you can't really download OBS on your iPad
I tried doing that shit or trying to um, I
Tried doing that shit, but that's it don't work. You gotta have that shit on a computer
Hold on something just popped up man
Fucking Alex man
Alex on some shit Alex, I guess it's uh, she's about to talk about beater
People trying to ride the wave
I ain't gonna say you tired of beta if you got beaters BKG
I'm not tired beta why people say I'm tired of beta
Who said that no, I mean accent he started beta, but
Beta really don't get old like that. I mean some things do get on repeat like same man that motherfucker be on repeat
but um, I
Don't know be this content
I see potential and beta you you you you you got potential to but you'd be you'd be quicker
you know thank you yeah yeah thank you but wait what do you say yeah you got potential
too man you got potential if you pass out and all that that's entertainment man whatever
you like to believe it or not man well
It's bad that way. I don't know. Do I know? Yes, the hell you do when you fucking lean forward
What so are you diagnosed with something like when you like when you when you when you move up and like
Slow, so when you go up and down and shit like you know me
when you Bob
What what is that called? Do you know?
Yeah, like you like if you get nervous you'll touch your face
You'll start looking around you'll start when your body will start moving back and forth like you're on a rocking chair
Rock yeah, I don't think you on any type of crazy drugs though, you know
Oh, yeah, I don't really think it ain't really worth doing no drug tests. I don't really think y'all know crazy drugs
I mean you already admitted you was on Adderall
I know I have before yeah
I
Don't know why this is not working. Okay. Oh, I might be working
I don't know. This is not working. I need to look in trying to
Download this music
Tell you man remember Sam Man said that he looking for another superstar
Psych might need Sam Man's next superstar. You hear me?
Somebody go get Sam Man because like he loves saying man
Yeah, right psyche. Yeah
You can be a superstar.
I love Sam here.
Superstar, AI, music.
Well, what do you mean?
I don't want to be like Sam as a locale, though.
What are you talking about?
Like, it sounds like something.
I mean, people thought that locale was a bad thing,
but I don't really think locale is a bad thing, bro.
Locals is like another like an entertainer. Like you got actors. You got motherfucking
Just different type of entertainers man low low cow is one of them
Yeah, I'm not saying you a locale, but I'm just saying locale ain't a bad thing, bro
Yeah, it is it's something that that is milk milk for content entertainment
And then there's kind of like this laptop like I kind of considered a joke and then so you don't like people laughing at you
Well, I think you know you can laugh. I don't care necessarily. I mean if people are you know, I mean it's a bit
You know, it's really doesn't benefit me to have people laughing at me
It does benefit you you make money what you mean you fucking been making boo boo bugs
So when there's drama over here and and and you might be a part of it or it might be people on your panel
but it's definitely a
You do benefit and I know this you you just want to benefit benefit benefit man
Like it's not wrong with it, but you definitely about
They got a benefit to it, but he benefit usually I'm saying
They don't make dollars. It don't make sense. It's something like that. I don't know this. I'm kind of like
Well, yeah
You like white girls, yeah, I've never dated a white girl
Yeah, but I I mean I've seen my friends date white girls and it wasn't looking too pretty man
Not nothing wrong with white girls. They some crazy bitches, huh?
They some crazy women man
Mm-hmm. I think this one of it one of my friends that I grew up with his fucking girlfriend ex-girl now
I think she locked up, but she fucking end up
Cutting his dick off and shit. Ah
Yeah
He dickless. Yeah, I was fucking like 23. I think we get we was the same age and he was dating this white girl
And she ended up cutting his dick over
Wait, what's up? Oh wait, what actually what's up?
I think there's an article on that shit, too
JT is jerking off in the backstage
What JT
Why was JT jerking off backstage? What the fuck?
I can hear you twice
Why the fuck would JT come out? I don't even I don't fuck with it
And it seemed like something wrong with that motherfuckers is one time he came up and saying oh, did I ever met you?
Eldo like motherfucker. We was arguing on beaty shit. Like how you forget that like
You ain't your fucking lady and I haven't seen his girl
Think she got her info got out there now. She's scared and shit
Where she might have got deported, I don't fucking know, you know, Trump didn't deport them off of us. She is a Mexican
Okay, I'm racing though. Yeah, I'm not
I still hear a double of you, but what are you trying to do?
I know you got your iPad in your phone, but...
I had to go into school.
Oh, you know what you can do, Si? You can mute one of them.
You can mute, like, if you got both of them up, if you're trying to do something, you can always mute one of them.
Sorry. Okay, ready to hear the song? I'm going to play something. Ready?
That film, yeah, background too.
Oh, shit, you got a new song?
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up the scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sides twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame this ain't your mama's podcast this a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob flashing on cam chat losing their minds my
We're getting gong, Alex taking flight It's wild, it's wrong, and we do it every
night Pays got him simping, heart's in the chat
But she ain't got time for a dude like that Diamond flirting hard, let the girls react
It's a freak show party, no filter, all facts
Yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight Alex tried a joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still cracking jokes
Slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow no rules just rolls
We pretend to play one hand on the mute of the letting it spray
and we're trending in the press welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob splashing on cam chat
losing their minds michael getting gong to alex taking flight it's wild it's wrong and we do it
every night page got him simping hearts in the chat though she ain't got time for a dude like that
diamond flirting hard let the girls react it's a freak show party no filter all facts yeah all facts
know the vibe
Like who made that who made that song who made that song? I did I did AI I did with AI
Yeah, you couldn't add me on there at all. I will you'll be in the next one you want to be
I'm one of the main motherfucking figures. Do you figure?
They are not entertaining enough to be, you know what I'm saying? Come on. Come on. Good. I'm just a point of man
You got flirty in there a page you got flirty in that month. Oh, you even got paid in there, too
Hear your part page
That's not paid
Page are you there?
That's not pay is that pay
So why'd you see her do she's a guy over maybe
Maybe that's what we have to see a computer
Maybe just don't tell me page of fucking training bro. Oh my god. Oh my god
She is she's no Chad y'all didn't just hear a guy when she
So so you didn't hear a guy
No, I mean
You guys hear man
I might just be made up
Yeah, but her shit be fucking up like that. So she'll probably come back
Okay
So so guys that's we're doing that the next song and I need suggestions, okay?
Well, I need to you guys help so I see you guys can like be a part of like the creation process about I need you to like
Give me some ideas. Okay, but anyway, so who's gonna be in the next song? We're gonna have whoever you have
We're gonna have let's have a
I think you should have on the next one you should have me
You should add Kate in there even though she a I mean it's still part of it, you know
What's going on? Just make sure you you end up like mentioning something about Kate like she farts when she's on live
So you can do something like that
or
Yeah, if Kate's on there, you definitely got a beat on her again. Okay. Okay. Yeah, maybe maybe Sam man and Barry
You know
So, I don't know. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna make a whole Lisa Jordan song, you know, I'm gonna send
And then the main song mentioned fish tacos I didn't hear nothing about fish time. We have to the fish fish tacos get fish tacos
Okay, as a top it
Because like you okay
I think what's been going on on your parents and I cook in
Yeah, help out Chad give me some ideas. Give me some ideas
Paging it again and
Also, I might put I make you some of the same themes like you know, there's oh, let's see who else I can say
Um
What about having beta, you know, because beta got her condo from her dad
What about beta getting pizzas
Okay
I'll do God and I'll put God in there too and I'll put spunky in there too. Okay, that'll be double enough people
Okay, yeah, I'm not sure
Can you can you talk to the chair? Oh, here's Chris. Oh, Crystal Marie too. I'll put Crystal Marie in the song
So you made a song to you. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but crystal and I'm off of you
Shout out to my girl crystal
Okay, oh you can't hear you crystal
Oh, yeah, we can't hear you darling
Guys talk for a second talk for a second, and I'll be right back. I'm gonna write the song and produce it real quick
I'll be like it'll take me three minutes. I'll be right back. Okay. Okay
Dan crystal crystal you looking like a fucking nine, bro. I
Mean, I'm not trying cuz I don't usually know come off like like like like this, but you definitely
Shout out to crystal
Hey, you can call me a simp all day, baby
We can't hear you crystal so picture it might be a headphone whatever you
Oh, we hear you page we hear you now
Crystal you fix your mic
Page did you fix your mic?
Goddamn it here by myself
Crystal come back up crystal
How you doing though page you good
Yeah
It's good. I like that song was pretty crazy, hey
This is the first song I did. I'll put this first one. I did on this is the first one
I made but I'll making another one right now. So just listen, but here's the first one I made
Like the rap one that we just listened to is quite catty
Okay, yeah, it's pretty cool. Thank you. I like I like the I like this one is this one is like more of the
I love you.
Open panel, nothing's ever planned
Just hearts on sleeves and raised hands
It's a circus, it's a prayer
It's the quiet truth laid bare
One minute love, the next a storm
Flirty diamond got us porn, bomb, bomb
But somehow we all belong
Bait her cries while the chat goes wild
Page rolls eyes, but she's begot
Everyone's got a story to sell
But no one leaves the carousel
It's a song
Yeah, that's not bad, but I like the first one better. This one. I know
Yeah, so this is oh, yeah, now we can see the difference. I mean, it's like, yeah
Yeah, it's my the last one I tried to write it said it was already violating the usage policy
So I have to rethink it. Okay. Oh, okay. Give me another minute. Yeah, but I'm working on it. I'll be right back
Shout out to the chat shout out to Amber in the building Vicky. I see you Vicky was good with you
Hopefully everybody having a good fucking what's today Monday? Oh
I'll probably be live myself. I might be live man sometime this week
Now just to try to get me get back on the flow man. I might do like like
Clip reviews and shit. I ain't gonna lie a trip cake got this thing going on this
Yeah, this series or whatever with the beta shit, you know
That shit was hilarious
And then I'll be beef has had to had his own version of
What's going on with with beta and
her getting
Her getting out walking up to that guy outside and running them off allegedly
The KK had a good live earlier today.
She had a, she exposed that one guy, Brandon Q.
He was, I didn't even know that either.
He was talking to some young, some young ass Abreeder.
That shit was weird as hell, no.
Okay guys come on backstage
Nobody. Oh, yeah, no Cal's backstage. Okay guys. Okay, the song is on its way
What's fucking go come on I knew I was gonna tell